Finding aid for University Herbarium (University of Michigan) Records, 1744-1745, 1851-1981, and 2001-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1744-1855; 1875-1959
  - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 1875-1959
    - S
      - Scott, J.M., 1944 (Box 15)
        (A.F. collecting & personal)
      - Scott, William Henry, 1958 (Box 15)
      - Sears, Mrs. Charles H. (Minnie S.), 1947 (Box 15)
      - Sears, Paul B., 1950-1955 (Box 15)
      - Seeber, R.R., 1951 (Box 15)
        (plant identification)
      - Seifriz, William, 1925-1946 (Box 15)
      - Sellew, Helen, 1957 (Box 15)
        (plant propagation)
      - "Sen", personal-Harvard (Box 15)
      - Sen Gupta, J.C., 1956 (Box 15)
        (Indian plant collections)
      - Senn, Harold A., 1932 (Box 15)
        (request)
      - Senninger, Earl J., 1958 (Box 15)
        (Fire & Prim. Agr.; Jehudi Ashmun)
      - Senstius, M.W., 1938 (Box 15)
      - Seward, Albert C., 1932 (Box 15)
        (lecture)
      - Seward, Patricia (Mrs. Benjamin S.) 1951-52, popcorn (Box 15)
      - Shacklette, Hansford T., 1941-1960 (Box 15)
        (student; Great Bear Lake exped;)
      - Shadle, Albert R., 1944-1946 (Box 15)
        (positions; see also: Wharton,)
      - Shah, Rajul, 1931-1933 (Box 15)
        (Barbour scholar; tobacco)
      - Shantz, Homer L., 1921-1957 (Box 15)
        (Fire & Prim. Agr.-Africa, etc.-Tree Name Comm.; see also West, Gladys F.; (photographic file))
      - Shapiro, H.L., 1958 (Box 15)
      - Shapiro, Philip J., 1945 (Box 15)
      - Shapiro, Seymour, 1946-1947 (Box 15)
      - Sharp, Aaron J. (Jack), 1936-1954 (Box 15)
        (fellowship; radioactivity effects; see also White, Stephen S.)
      - Shaw, Wilfred B., 1936-1948 (Box 15)
        (Encyclopedia of the U of M;)
      - Shear, Cornelius L., 1952-1955 (Box 15)
        (biographical, Asa Gray Bulletin)
      - Shear, Cornelius L., Autobiographical notes & other material re C.L.S. (Box 15)
      - Sheldon, John L., 1910 (Box 15)
      - Sheldon, Theodore, 1946 (Box 15)
        (Philippines-Aguinaldo-revolutionary material)
      - Shelesnyak, M.C. (Box 15)
      - Shellabear, Joseph L., 1934 (Box 15)
      - Shellabear, W.G., 1934-1936 (Box 15)
        (Batak, Sumatra, Philippines)
      - Shellenberger, John A., 1945 (Box 15)
        (chemical education in Argentina)
      - Shepard, Arthur L., 1934-1945 (Box 15)
        (Philippines, A.F. collecting)
      - Shepardson, Whitney H., 1926 (Box 15)
        (International Educ. Board-Kulkarni-fellowship)
      - Sherff, Earl E., 1937; 1940 (Box 15)
        (Bidens, genus concept)
      - Shipment of Curios-Japan, 1926-1927 (Box 15)
      - Shirling, Mrs. A.E., 1955 (Box 15)
      - Shirling, Elwood B., 1946 (Box 15)
      - Shoemaker, Daniel N., 1933 (Box 15)
        (Helianthus)
      - Shor, Jean & Franc, 1955 (Box 15)
      - Short, Ena D., 1944 (Box 15)
        (Argentina; rubber)
      - Showalter, William J., 1928 (Box 15)
        (science & religion)
      - Shrader, J.H. (Box 15)
      - Shreve, Forrest, 1934-1940 (Box 15)
        (Mexican botany)
      - Shufeldt, P.W., 1931-1933 (Box 15)
        (Percy Gentle's collecting-)
      - Shull, A. Franklin, 1918-1932 (Box 15)
        (department affairs)
      - Shull, George H., 1918-1933 (Box 15)
        ("Genetics"; Oenothera; The Galton & Mendel Mem. Fund)
      - Sigma Xi, 1938-1945 (Box 15)
      - Silayan, Hilarion (Box 15)
        (see Uichanco)
      - Sim, Douglas, 1955-1956 (Box 15)
      - Simmons, Emory G., 1946 (Box 15)
      - Simms, S.C.S., 1929 (Box 15)
      - Simon, Donald A., 1944 (Box 15)
      - Simonpietri, Andr; C., 1956 (Box 16)
      - Simonson, Roy W., 1957 (Box 16)
      - Simpson, Charles T., 1910 (Box 16)
      - Simpson, Helen F., 1944-1947 (Box 16)
      - Simpson, Walter M., 1942 (Box 16)
      - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1915-1947 (Box 16)
      - Skeels, Homer C., 1920-1934 (Box 16)
        (plant culture)
      - Skutch, Alexander F., 1936-1938 (Box 16)
      - Sleator, W.W., 1938 (Box 16)
        (Ginkgo)
      - Slevin, Joseph R., 1940 (Box 16)
        (historical)
      - Slocom, Arthur W., 1929 (Box 16)
      - Slooten, D.T., 1932 (Box 16)
        (request for reprints)
      - Small, John K., 1911 (Box 16)
        (request, Euphorbia)
      - Small, L.K., 1942 (Box 16)
        (agar)
      - Smiley, Nixon, 1952 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Albert C., 1944-1952 (Box 16)
        (publications, loans)
      - Smith, Alexander H., 1928-1946 (Box 16)
        (student-faculty)
      - Smith, A.H., 1948 (Box 16)
        (anthropologist)
      - Smith, Benjamin W., 1936 (Box 16)
        (Dioscorea)
      - Smith, Clarence, 1931 (Box 16)
        (bacteriacide)
      - Smith, Charles Piper, 1903-1946; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Smith, Dent, 1956 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Ernest C., 1939 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Erwin F., 1917-1920 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Frank H., Oenothera (Box 16)
      - Smith, Mrs. Franklin W., 1944 (Box 16)
      - Smith, G. Herbert, 1946 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Helen V., 1932 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Hugh B., 1925 (Box 16)
        (1944-46)
      - Smith, Ira M., 1947 (Box 16)
        (thanks for talk)
      - Smith, Johanne E., 1947 (Box 16)
      - Smith, J. Russell, 1956 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Lyman B., 1932-1947 (Box 16)
      - Smith, L.J., 1947 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Marvin H., 1945 (Box 16)
      - Smith, M.P., 1929 (Box 16)
        (personal-rent, Thomson, Ga.)
      - Smith, R.A., 1928 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Russell A., 1946 (Box 16)
        (student recommendation)
      - Smith, Mrs. R.K. (Lura McLane), 1936 (Box 16)
        (plant collection, Korea)
      - Smith, Shirley W., 1917-1945 (Box 16)
        (see also Botanical Gardens-)
      - Smith, T. Lynn, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Warren D., 1947-1948 (Box 16)
      - Smith, Wilbur F., 1954 (Box 16)
      - Smithsonian Institution, 1940 (Box 16)
        (see also Greene, E.L., "Landmarks";)
      - Snyder, Harold E., 1947 (Box 16)
      - Snyder, Leon C., 1936 (Box 16)
      - Society for the Study of Evolution, 1946 (Box 16)
        (charter member, 1 card from Ernst Mayr, Secretary)
      - Society for the Study of Speciation, 1946 (Box 16)
        (announcement, 1 letter from Alfred E. Emerson)
      - Sohmas, H., 1937 (Box 16)
      - Soost, R.K., 1945 (Box 16)
        (A.F. collecting-students)
      - Soule, Gilmore W., 1945 (Box 16)
      - Soule, Malcolm, 1940-1942 (Box 16)
        (Sigma Xi lecture; contributions to war effort; see also Taylor, Norman)
      - South Africa, 1955 (Box 16)
      - Southeast Asia Institute, 1946-1948 (Box 16)
      - South Pacific Commission, 1955 (Box 16)
      - Southworth Company, Publishers, 1920 (Box 16)
      - "Spanish Prisoner Swindle", 1940 (Box 16)
      - Sparshott, E.N., 1936 (Box 16)
        (Testudinaria)
      - Sparrow, Frederick K., 1936-1950 (Box 16)
      - Spaulding, R.M., 1957 (Box 16)
        (Japanese philately)
      - Spencer, Henry D. (Box 16)
        (see Northern Nutgrowers Association)
      - Spencer, J.E., 1955-1957 (Box 16)
        (shifting agriculture)
      - Spencer, R.D., 1947 (Box 16)
        (staffing-U. Philippines)
      - Spillenaar, G., 1919-1920 (Box 16)
      - Spillman, William J., 1917 (Box 16)
        (cowpea pigment)
      - Spongberg, "Bun", 1933 (Box 16)
      - Sponsler, O.L., 1940 (Box 16)
      - Spragg, Frank A., 1919 (Box 16)
      - Springer, Stuart (Box 16)
      - Stacy, Osborne E., 1948 (Box 16)
      - Stamp, L. Dudley, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Standley, Paul C., 1916-1946 (Box 16)
        (plants)
      - Stanfield, Silas W., 1910 (Box 16)
      - Stanley, George, 1945 (Box 16)
        (geology)
      - Stark, H.E., 1936 (Box 16)
        (wood samples)
      - Stauffer, J., 1950 (Box 16)
        (Oenothera-student problem)
      - Stearns, Frances, 1931-1938 (Box 16)
        (Crataegus, Emma Cole)
      - Stearns, Frederick & Co., 1920 (Box 16)
        (drug plants)
      - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, 1928 (Box 16)
        (position at Michigan)
      - Steele, Edward S., 1922 (Box 16)
        (Lacinaria)
      - Steere, James H., 1945 (Box 16)
      - Steere, Joseph Beal, "I am an agnostic" (Box 16)
        (1 note & ms, see also Special Interests, J.B.Steere-Letters)
      - Steere, Russell L., 1941-1956 (Box 16)
        (student, war experience, A.F.)
      - Steere, William C., 1927-1956 (Box 16)
        (see also White, Stephen S.; & Wilcov, H.H., Jr.)
      - Steidemann, Robert, 1945 (Box 16)
      - Steidtmann, Waldo E., 1928-1946 (Box 16)
      - Steigerwaldt, Edward, 1945 (Box 16)
      - Stein, Peter, 1947 (Box 16)
      - Steiner, Erich E., 1940-1947 (Box 16)
      - Steiner, M.L., 1948 (Box 16)
        (Philippines-orchids)
      - Stephans, James C. (Box 16)
      - Stephans, Walter T., 1943-1946 (Box 16)
        (guayule-Uruguay)
      - Stephens, Charles R., 1923 (Box 16)
        (plants for propagation)
      - Stephens, J.L., 1956 (Box 16)
      - Stephenson, T.A., 1945 (Box 16)
        (places for collecting)
      - Sternberg, Hilgard O'R., Fire & Prim. Agr. (Box 16)
      - Stevens, George H., 1925 (Box 16)
        (wood oil exhibits & pictures)
      - Stevens, J.L., 1956 (Box 16)
      - Stevens, Neil E., 1945-1947 (Box 16)
        (National Herbarium)
      - Stevens, Orin Alva, 1932-1951 (Box 16)
        (see also Asa Gray Bulletin)
      - Stevenson, Fred G., 1936 (Box 16)
        (Michigan W.P.A.)
      - Stevenson, John A., 1948 (Box 16)
        (books for Philippines; see also U.S.D.A.-B.P.I.-Foreign Seed & Plant Introduction)
      - Steward, Albert N., 1924; 1932 (Box 16)
        (seeds & fruits from China;)
      - Stewart, Alban, 1909 (Box 16)
      - Stewart, James B. (Box 16)
      - Stewart, Josephine L. Martin, 1938 (Box 16)
      - Stewart, Lenoir, 1958 (Box 16)
      - Stewart, Omer C., 1955 (Box 16)
      - Stewart, Ralph R., 1933; 1945 (Box 16)
        (plant specimens, A.F. collecting)
      - Stewart, Richard H., 1940 (Box 16)
      - Stigler, Robert, 1955 (Box 16)
      - Stiles, K.A., 1934 (Box 16)
      - Stilwell, L.W., 1910 (Box 16)
        (Rhus-collecting)
      - Stockard, Alfred H., 1934-1945 (Box 16)
        (Michigan Academy Papers, Biological Station)
      - Stockberger, Warner W. (Box 16)
        (see U.S.D.A.-B.P.I.)
      - Stoker, Susan, 1932 (Box 16)
        (seed lists-collector)
      - Stone, Fred S., 1955 (Box 16)
        (mangoes and how to eat them)
      - Stone, J.Herbert, 1955 (Box 16)
        (preservation of natural areas)
      - Stone, Marshall H., 1943-1951 (Box 16)
        (philately-India, Asia)
      - Storbeck, Ivan, 1945 (Box 16)
        (A.F. collecting, philately)
      - Stork, H.E., 1932 (Box 16)
      - Storm, Colton, 1949 (Box 16)
        (see also Hunt, Mrs. R.A.)
      - Stover, Leon E., 1956 (Box 16)
      - Stratton, Robert, 1941 (Box 16)
        (information re Botanical Garden)
      - Studholme, J.M., 1933 (Box 16)
        (The Living Age)
      - Sturgis, Cyrus C., 1927; 1939 (Box 16)
      - Sturrock, Ruth Mary, 1946 (Box 16)
      - Sturtevant, Alfred H., 1922-1930 (Box 16)
        (seeds & plants; genetics)
      - Sudlers, A.T., 1927 (Box 16)
      - Suenaga, Hideta, 1957 (Box 16)
        (Arenga)
      - Suggs, Robert, 1956 (Box 16)
        (advice on travel to and collecting)
      - Suksdorf, Wilhelm W., 1908-27(1952) plant collections (Box 16)
      - Sullivan, L.A., 1957 (Box 16)
      - Sullivan, Ray E., 1947 (Box 16)
        (canoe trip-West Indies)
      - Sumatra, 1926-1934 (Box 16)
        (re Sumatra)
      - Sumatran language (Box 16)
      - Sun, T.P., 1937 (Box 16)
        (Barbour Scholar)
      - Susie, 1936 (Box 16)
      - Sussman, Alfred S., Phoenix (Box 16)
      - Sutherland, G.B.B.M., 1935 (Box 16)
        (administrative)
      - Svenson, Henry K., 1952 (Box 16)
      - Svihla, Ruth D., 1930-1942 (Box 16)
      - Swallen, Jason R., 1931-1952 (Box 16)
      - Swami, S.R., 1958 (Box 16)
      - Swingle, Charles F., 1936-1945 (Box 16)
      - Swingle, Dorothy J., 1936 (Box 16)
      - Swingle, Walter T. (& Maude K.), 1936-1957 (Box 16)
        (includes A.G.B. & biographical material)
      - Swinton, R., 1945-1954 (Box 16)
        (Silliman, Far Eastern Univ.; Philippines)
      - Sykes, Gilbert, 1954-1955 (Box 16)
        ("big trees", photographs of Sonoran desert, Baja Calif., cacti)
      - Szyszlo, Vitold, 1956 (Box 16)
    - T
      - Tamayo, Francisco, 1956-1957 (Box 16)
      - Tan, Esperanza & Consuelo, 1950 (Box 16)
        (?, Philippines)
      - Tan, Vidal A., 1952 (Box 16)
      - Tapping, T.Hawley, 1933-1949 (Box 16)
        (Alumni Association, U. of M.)
      - Taxes-Cambridge, D.C., Georgia & Michigan (Box 16)
      - Taylor, Albert B., 1945-1946 (Box 16)
      - Taylor, Carl C. (Box 16)
        (see U.S.D.A.-Bur. Agr. Econ)
      - Taylor, Frank B., 1929 (Box 16)
      - Taylor, F.O., 1934-1937 (Box 16)
        (Parke, Davis herbarium & library)
      - Taylor, Norman, 1945-1951 (Box 16)
        (Cinchona Products Inst.; E.L.Greene-Torreya)
      - Taylor, Wesley Foster, 1944 (Box 16)
        (botanical journals)
      - Taylor, William A. (Box 17)
      - Taylor, William Randolph, 1930-1957 (Box 17)
      - Telford, Gertrude, 1935-1938 (Box 17)
        (?, personal-Burma)
      - Teninga, Lucille, 1945 (Box 17)
        (teaching)
      - Teuscher, Henry, 1948 (Box 17)
        (O.N.R. Project-Great Bear Lake-James Kucyniak)
      - Thach, Charles C., 1912 (Box 17)
        (invitation-Alabama)
      - Tharp, Benjamin C., 1932; 1937 (Box 17)
        (Mueller's collection, Eragrostis)
      - Thielen, Irene T., 1923 (Box 17)
        (genealogy (Potter)
      - Thivierge, A., 1954 (Box 17)
      - Thivy, Francesca, 1944-1949 (Box 17)
        (student & see also Fellows, K.A.)
      - Thomas, William K., 1958 (Box 17)
        (collecting, birches)
      - Thomas, William L. (Box 17)
        (see Wenner-Gren Foundation)
      - Thomas, W. Stephen, 1946 (Box 17)
      - Thompson, David H., 1938 (Box 17)
        (see Velasquez, Gregorio T.,)
      - Thompson, Jerome, 1947 (Box 17)
      - Thompson, Joan M., 1951 (Box 17)
      - Thompson, Paul W., 1946-1958 (Box 17)
      - Thompson, T.S., 1956 (Box 17)
      - Thomson, Ga., City Clerk, 1925 (Box 17)
        (personal-cemetery deed)
      - Thomson, Ga.., 1st National Bank, 1924 (Box 17)
        (property deed)
      - Thomson, George W., 1945-1946 (Box 17)
        (amateur botanist)
      - Thomson, Harriet W., 1955 (Box 17)
        (Conservation; 3-Sisters Wilderness)
      - Thone, Frank, 1945 (Box 17)
      - Thornber, John J., 1910 (Box 17)
      - Thornborough, Albert A., 1947 (Box 17)
      - Thorne, Robert F., 1946 (Box 17)
      - Thornthwaite, C.W., 1936 (Box 17)
        (soil conservation)
      - Thorvold, C.A., 1956 (Box 17)
      - Thrall, Will H., 1954 (Box 17)
        ("big trees"-papers; see also Vernon, C.)
      - Thuma, Burton D., 1951-1955 (Box 17)
      - Tichelman, G.L., 1938-1945 (Box 17)
        (anthropology-war in Holland;)
      - Tiffany, Harold S., 1928-1932 (Box 17)
        (student-Botanical Garden)
      - Tiffany, Lewis Hanford, 1949 (Box 17)
        (Hao-Jan Chu-help for Chinese)
      - Tilden, Josephine E., 1921-1939 (Box 17)
        (Index Algarum, Pacific algae)
      - "Time" Inc., 1956 (Box 17)
        (cultivation of wildflowers)
      - Tinkham, Ernest R., 1946 (Box 17)
        (collecting-Lower California)
      - Tinkham, Russ J., 1942 (Box 17)
        (request for recommendation;)
      - Tobler, Friedrich, 191+6 (Box 17)
      - Tiwari, S.D.N., 1957 (Box 17)
      - Tolstead, W.L., 1944 (Box 17)
      - Tompkins, L.D. (Box 17)
      - Tonne, Erwin, 1949 (Box 17)
        (petrified bananas)
      - Toralballa, L.V., 1959 (Box 17)
        (American-Philippine Foundation)
      - Torres, Heloisa A., 1946 (Box 17)
      - Torres Rojas, Rulon, 1945 (Box 17)
      - Torrey Botanical Club, membership (Box 17)
      - Totten, Henry R., 1945 (Box 17)
        (SPEIS-war effort)
      - Toulouse, Julian Harrison, 1939 (Box 17)
        (invitation to speak-Toledo)
      - Townsend, Charles W., 1911 (Box 17)
        (bogs; see also U.S.D.A.-B.P.I.)
      - Tozzer, Alfred W., 1934 (Box 17)
      - Tracy, Samuel Mills, 1910 (Box 17)
        (Rhus; see also Photograph Album)
      - Train, Percy, 1933 (Box 17)
      - Trapido, Harold, 1948 (Box 17)
      - Travelers Insurance, 1951 (Box 17)
        (automobile)
      - Traylor, M.A., 1948 (Box 17)
        (scientists in Armed Forces)
      - Treadwell, G.B., 1956 (Box 17)
      - Treichel, George W., 1955 (Box 17)
      - Trelease, William, 1918-1940 (Box 17)
      - Tristan da Cunha, 1949-1950 (Box 17)
      - Trochain, J.L., 1956 (Box 17)
      - Troyer, Maurice E., 1950 (Box 17)
        (recommendations, education)
      - True, Rodney H., 1920-1933 (Box 17)
        (see also U.S.D.A.-Bureau of Plant Industry-Plant Physiological)
      - Trullinger, Robert W., 1947 (Box 17)
      - Tryon, Katherine, 1950 (Box 17)
        (student-Phoenix project,)
      - Tryon, Rolla M., 1942 (Box 17)
        (exchange, Pteridium)
      - Tschermak-Seysenegg, Erich, 1947 (Box 17)
      - Tseng, Cheng Kwei, 1940-1945 (Box 17)
        (student, marine algae, Koelz collection, Chand collection, seaweed colloid, philately)
      - Tsui, Cheng, 1946-1948 (Box 17)
        (student-language requirement)
      - Tsui, You-Wen, 1947-1948 (Box 17)
        (see also Tsui, Cheng)
      - Tubb, J.A., 1957 (Box 17)
      - Tucker, Clarence M., 1937 (Box 17)
        (position at Missouri)
      - Tupper, Walter W., 1915-1939 (Box 17)
        (wood anatomy, personal problems)
      - Tuthill, H.A., 1957 (Box 17)
        (philately; sweet potato)
      - Tuttle, Allen E., 1947 (Box 17)
      - Twitchell, Doris, 1932 (Box 17)
      - Twitchell, Robert R., 1933 (Box 17)
      - Twohy, James, 1945 (Box 17)
        (student-recommendation;)
    - U
      - Uhvitz, Rachel, 1932-1946 (Box 17)
      - Uichanco, Leopoldo B., 1938-1950 (Box 17)
        (Philippines; see also Guggenheim)
      - Umbach, Levi M., 1910 (Box 17)
      - United Nations, U.S. Delegation, 1955 (Box 17)
      - (United States) American Consular Service, 1918 (Box 17)
        (imports,)
      - (United States) Army Map Service, 1950-1951 (Box 17)
      - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1948-1950 (Box 17)
      - United States Department of Agriculture, 1909-1955
        - Agricultural Research Administration, 1944-1949 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Agricultural Economics, 1943 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Entomology & Plant quarantine 35 items, 1930-1955 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry, 1920-193 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry-Forage Crop Investigations, 1920 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry-Foreign Seed & Plant Introduction, 1912-1937 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry-Plant Exploration & Introduction, 1938-1946 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry -- Plant Physiological, etc Investigation, 1909-1920 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry-Rubber Investigations, 1920-1945 (Box 17)
        - Bureau of Plant Industry-Sugar Plant Investigations, 1919-1920 (Box 17)
        - Office of Foreign Agricultural Relations, 1944-1955 (Box 17)
        - Foreign Agricultural Service, 1955 (Box 17)
        - Forest Service, 1931-1958 (Box 17)
          (see also Dayton, W.A.)
        - Bureau of Soils, 1909 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Department of the Interior-U.S. Board on Geographical Names, 1947 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Department of the Interior-Geological Survey, 1929-1956 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Department of the Interior-National Park Service, 1951-1954 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Department of Justice, 1942-1946 (Box 17)
        (Foreign agents, immigration)
      - U.S. Office of Naval Research, 1947-1951 (Box 17)
        (Radiation & Plant Heredity)
      - U.S. Post Office Department, Philately, postal censorship (Box 17)
      - United States House of Representatives, 1937-1944 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Rubber Plantations (Box 17)
      - United States Senate, 1938-1947 (Box 17)
      - United States Department of State (Box 17)
      - U.S. Dept. State-Fulbright Funds (Box 17)
      - U.S. Office of Strategic Services, 1945 (Box 17)
      - United States Treasury Department-Customs Service (Box 17)
      - University Club, 1938 (Box 17)
      - University of Michigan News Service (Box 17)
      - Uvarov, B.P., 1957 (Box 17)
    - V
      - V. & E. Manufacturing Co., 1949 (Box 17)
        (compass improvement)
      - Valenzuela, Patrocinio, 1936-1952 (Box 17)
        (Philippines; see also Eighth)
      - Vallus, Hubert (Box 17)
        (see U.S. Dept. of Justice)
      - Vandenberg, Arthur H., 1945-1947 (Box 17)
        (see also U.S. Senate)
      - VanderSchalie, Henry, 1957; 1944 (Box 17)
      - VanderVelde, L.G., 1938-1946 (Box 17)
        (Mich. Historical Collections)
      - VanderWegen, Wright, 1945 (Box 17)
      - VanDyke, Henry, 1948 (Box 17)
        (armed forces)
      - VanSchaack, George B., 1946 (Box 17)
        (placement)
      - Van's Nursery & Landscape Service, 1945 (Box 17)
      - Van Steenis, Cornelis G.G.J., 1947-1952 (Box 17)
        (see also Nat. Res. Council, Pac. Sci. Bd.; Flora Malesiana)
      - Van Steenis-Kruseman, M.J., 1955 (Box 17)
      - Van Tyne, Josselyn, 1932-1951 (Box 17)
      - Varrelman, Ferdinand A., 1936-1944 (Box 17)
        (Nat'l. Arboretum & Bot. Gard.)
      - Velasquez, Carmen C., 1937 (Box 17)
      - Velasquez, Gregorio T., 1956-1958 (Box 17)
        (student; Philippines; see also)
      - Verdoorn, Frans, 1954-1957 (Box 17)
        (Chronica Botanica; Botanical)
      - Vergeer, Teunis, 1949-1950 (Box 17)
        (effects of radiation)
      - Vernon, Charles, Giant Alders in Angeles Nat. Forest; Sierra Pelona Oak (Box 17)
      - Vick, Robert A., 1947 (Box 18)
        (A.F. collecting; directions)
      - Victorin, Marie, 1940 (Box 18)
        (palms, Cuba)
      - Viehoever, Arno, 1937 (Box 18)
        (experimental plants)
      - Villaflores, Herculana, 1936-1937 (Box 18)
        (Philippines; algae)
      - Villar, Ernesto, 1938; 1949 (Box 18)
      - Viosca, Percy, 1956 (Box 18)
      - Virkus, Frederick Adams, 1940 (Box 18)
        ("Compendium of American Genealogy")
      - Vogt, Frederick H., 1950 (Box 18)
        (re Roy Jervis)
      - Volwiler, E.H., 1946 (Box 18)
        ("cepharanthin"; Abbott Laboratories)
      - von Broembsen, H.H., 1956 (Box 18)
      - von Hagen, W. (Box 18)
        (see Expedition: Darwin Mem.)
      - Vonnegut, Alex, 1910-1939 (Box 18)
      - von Reis, Siri, 1952-1954 (Box 18)
        (Leguminosae; Ekman; "El Caballero de las Montanas" translation; preliminary biography of Ekman; "Expedicion Onate"-transl.)
      - Voorhoeve, P., 1939-1956 (Box 18)
        (linguistics, Sumatra)
      - Vosburgh, Frederick G., 1940, 1955 (Box 18)
        (National Geographic; linguistics)
      - Voss, Edward G., 1948; 1954 (Box 18)
      - Voth, Paul D., 1950 (Box 18)
        ("Newsletter" -- Chicago)
    - W
      - Wadmond, Samuel C., 1951 (Box 18)
        (plant collection-herbarium)
      - Wagner, Florence Signaigo, 1943 (Box 18)
        (Bartlett office)
      - Wagner, Kenneth A., 1946-1951 (Box 18)
      - Wagner, Philip L., 1956 (Box 18)
      - Wagner, Warren H., Quercus (Box 18)
      - Wagnon, Bargyla Rateaver (Box 18)
        (see Rateaver, Bargyla)
      - Wagnon, Harvey Keith, 1945-1951 (Box 18)
      - Walcott, C.D., 1919; 1921 (Box 18)
        (re Greene, E.L. "Landmarks")
      - Walcott, Gordon B. 1946, 1957, 1931 publication, 1931-1957 (Box 18)
        (position; Source BooksWaldbott, George L.,)
      - Walker, Egbert H., 1928-1939 (Box 18)
        (bibliography of Chinese botany; Koelz collections; Sumatran plants, etc.)
      - Walker, Egbert H., 1940-1945 (Box 18)